

Marcin Jurczak

Gdańsk, Poland

【 (+48) 602-858-994 | ■ marcin.jurczak@pm.me | 🖸 marcinjurczak | 🛅 marcin-jurczak

About me

Experienced Infrastructure and DevOps Engineer with a passion for automation, containerization and continuous integration. Interested in learning new technologies, right now focusing mainly on Cloud solutions. Linux tinkerer and Vim enthusiast, who enjoys to customize all of the development environment.

Professional Experience _____

Intel Technology Poland

Gdańsk, Poland

INFRASTRUCTURE AND DEVOPS ENGINEER

Jul. 2022 — Present

- · Designed and configured self-hosted GitHub Actions runners infrastructure for both Linux and Windows environments, optimizing resource utilization and reliability.
- · Architected and implemented GitHub Actions CI workflows for multiple projects, automating build and test processes
- · Implemented Docker containerization across multiple CI pipelines, ensuring consistent development environments and reducing environmentrelated issues
- · Integrated Coverity static code analysis tool into CI pipelines, establishing automated quality gates that reduced production defects and improved code quality
- · Conducted technical training sessions for multiple teams on static analysis tools and CI/CD best practices
- Developed and maintained extensive technical documentation for DevOps processes and procedures, improving team onboarding time
- · Proactively proposed and implemented improvements to enhance pipeline performance and reliability

Intel Technology Poland Gdańsk, Poland

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Mar. 2020 — Jun. 2022

- Designed and maintained Jenkins CI pipelines for multiple projects
- · Optimized and enhanced build systems for multiple internal tools, improving build efficiency and reliability
- Successfully migrated over 30 source code repositories from TeamForge to GitHub while maintaining code integrity
- · Conducted introductory GitHub training sessions for multiple development teams, improving version control practices and team efficiency
- · Performed regular code reviews and contributed to internal tool development
- Developed sample application using internal SDK, showcasing understanding of best software development practices

Education

GUT (Gdansk University of Technology)

Gdańsk, Poland

M.Sc. IN INFORMATICS

Mar. 2021 — Jun. 2022

· Thesis: Programming the front end applications with ELM language

GUT (Gdansk University of Technology)

Gdańsk, Poland

B.Sc. IN INFORMATICS

Oct. 2017 — Feb. 2021

• Thesis: Distributed Online Judging System

Technical Skills_

Programming

DevOps Jenkins

GitHub Actions Python

Additional

• • • • Ansible Terraform Bash

Linux

Docker Kubernetes •••• C/C++

Honors & Awards

1st place, Zombathon - for building ToyShare application Hackathon organized by Aspire Systems and the GUT's .NET Group Gdańsk, Poland

l agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

MARCIN JURCZAK · CURRICULUM VITAE DECEMBER 20, 2024